Guide to the John R. Mott Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- General Correspondence, Series I
  - Alphabetical listing
    - Dietz, W.E., 1948-1951 (Box 22, Folder 409)
    - Diffendorfer, Ralph E., 1935-1940 (Box 23, Folder 410)
    - Diffendorfer, Ralph E., 1941-1942 (Box 23, Folder 411)
    - Diffendorfer, Ralph E., 1943-1946 (Box 23, Folder 412)
    - Diffendorfer, Ralph E., 1947-1952, nd (Box 23, Folder 413)
    - Dingman, Russell G., 1933-1953 (Box 23, Folder 414)
    - Dix, Philo C., 1940-1944 (Box 23, Folder 415)
    - Dixon, Leonard A., 1913-1950 (Box 23, Folder 416)
    - Dodds, J. Leroy, 1944-1947 (Box 23, Folder 417)
    - Dodd, William E., 1934 (Box 23, Folder 418)
    - Dodge, Bayard, 1923-1953 (Box 23, Folder 419)
    - Dodge, Cleveland E., 1927-1936 (Box 23, Folder 420)
    - Dodge, Cleveland E., 1940-1941 (Box 23, Folder 421)
    - Dodge, Cleveland E., 1942-1946 (Box 23, Folder 422)
    - Dodge, Cleveland E., 1947-1954, nd (Box 23, Folder 423)
    - Dodge, Cleveland H., 1889-1907 (Box 23, Folder 424)
    - Dodge, Cleveland H., 1908-1909 (Box 23, Folder 425)
    - Dodge, Cleveland H., 1910-1913 (Box 23, Folder 426)
    - Dodge, Cleveland H., 1914-1919 (Box 23, Folder 427)
    - Dodge, Cleveland H., 1924-1925 (Box 23, Folder 428)
    - Cleveland H. Dodge Foundation, 1917-1941 (Box 23, Folder 429)
    - Cleveland H. Dodge Foundation, 1942-1954 (Box 23, Folder 430)
    - Dodge, D. Stuart, 1905-1916 (Box 23, Folder 431)
    - Dodge, El izabeth W. (see also: Elizabeth Dodge Huntington), 1915 (Box 23, Folder 432)
    - Dodge, Grace H., 1904-1905 (Box 24, Folder 433)
    - Dodge, Grace H., 1906-1911 (Box 24, Folder 434)
    - Dodge, Grace H., 1912-1914 (Box 24, Folder 435)
    - Dodge, Grace H., 1922, nd (Box 24, Folder 436)
    - Dodge, Grace Parish, 1928-1948, nd (Box 24, Folder 437)
    - Dodge, H. E., 1900-1911 (Box 24, Folder 438)
    - Dodge, M. Hartley, 1942-1944 (Box 24, Folder 439)
    - Dodge, Sarah H., 1904 (Box 24, Folder 440)
    - Dodge, William E., 1900-1902, nd (Box 24, Folder 441)
    - Dole, Andrew, 1925-1945 (Box 24, Folder 442)
    - Dollar, Robert, 1921-1933 (Box 24, Folder 443)
    - Dome, Arthur E., 1950-1954 (Box 24, Folder 444)
    - Douglas', H. Pall, 1934-1948 (Box 24, Folder 445)
    - Drummond, Henry (to C.K. Ober), 1887 (Box 24, Folder 446)
    - Dulles, John Foster, 1942-1948 (Box 24, Folder 447)
    - Dun, Angus, 1942-1954 (Box 24, Folder 448)
    - Dunlavy, Edwin W., 1947 (Box 24, Folder 449)
    - Dupre, Huntley, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 450)
    - Durgin, Russell L., 1940-1949 (Box 24, Folder 451)
    - Durgin, Russell L., 1949-1952 (Box 24, Folder 452)
    - Durham, Eugene, 1940-1944, nd (Box 24, Folder 453)
    - Dwight, Henry 0., 1900 (Box 24, Folder 454)
    - Ea - Ec (Box 25, Folder 455)
    - Ed - Ek (Box 25, Folder 456)
    - E1 (Box 25, Folder 457)
    - Em - En (Box 25, Folder 458)
    - Er - Eu (Box 25, Folder 459)
    - Er - Eu (Box 25, Folder 459)
    - Ev - Ey (Box 25, Folder 460)
    - Eagan, John J. and Susan, 1918-1953 (Box 25, Folder 461)
    - Earhart, Harry B., 1937-1952 (Box 25, Folder 462)
    - Easton, Addie, 1940-1954 (Box 25, Folder 463)
    - Ebara, Soroku, 1913 (Box 25, Folder 464)
    - Ebel, E.J., 1896 (Box 25, Folder 465)
    - Eberhardt, Charles R., 1948-1950 (Box 25, Folder 466)
    - Ebisawa, Akira, 1933-1952 (Box 25, Folder 467)
    - Eddy, Brewer, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 468)
    - Eddy, George Sherwood, 1904-1906 (Box 25, Folder 469)
    - Eddy, George Sherwood, 1910-1923 (Box 25, Folder 470)
    - Eddy, George Sherwood, 1926-1941 (Box 25, Folder 471)
    - Eddy, George Sherwood, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 472)
    - Eddy, George Sherwood, 1944-1952, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 473)
    - Edinburgh House Press (see: Wm. A. Bennett)
    - Edwards, Dwight W., 1941-1952 (Box 25, Folder 474)
    - Eidem, Erling, 1942-1950 (Box 25, Folder 475)
    - Elias, M.K., 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 476)
    - Elliott, Arthur J., 1910- 1942 (Box 26, Folder 477)
    - Elliott, Arthur J., 1943 (Box 26, Folder 478)
    - Elliott, Arthur J., 1944-1952 (Box 26, Folder 479)
    - Elliott, Arthur Roland, 1938-1940 (Box 26, Folder 480)
    - Elliott, Arthur Roland, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 481)
    - Elliott, Arthur Roland, 1943-1945, nd (Box 26, Folder 482)
    - Eliot, Samuel A., 1917 (Box 26, Folder 483)
    - Ellis, George W., 1944 (Box 26, Folder 484)
    - Emery, Theodore E., 1941-1949 (Box 26, Folder 485)
    - Engberg, Gunner, 1924-1947 (Box 26, Folder 486)
    - Espy, R.H. Edwin, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 487)
    - Espy, R.H. Edwin, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 488)
    - Espy, R.H. Edwin, 1943-1945 (Box 26, Folder 489)
    - Espy, R.H. Edwin, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 490)
    - Espy, R.H. Edwin, 1947-1948 (Box 26, Folder 491)
    - Espy, R.H. Edwin, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 492)
    - Espy, R.H. Edwin, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 493)
    - Espy, R.H. Edwin, 1952-1953 (Box 27, Folder 494)
    - Espy, R.H. Edwin, 1954-1955, nd (Box 27, Folder 495)
    - Estabrook and Co., 1940-1942 (Box 27, Folder 496)
    - Estabrook and Co., 1943-1946 (Box 27, Folder 497)
    - Estabrook and Co., 1947-1951 (Box 27, Folder 498)
    - Estabrook and Co., 1952-1954 (Box 27, Folder 499)
    - Eulogius, Metropolitan of the Russian Orthodox Church in Western Europe, 1933-1939 (Box 27, Folder 500)
    - Ewald, Charles J., 1902-1922 (Box 27, Folder 501)
    - Ewald, Charles J., 1924-1925 (Box 27, Folder 502)
    - Ewald, Charles J., 1928-1952 (Box 27, Folder 503)
    - Fag - Fal (Box 28, Folder 504)
    - Fan-- Fea (Box 28, Folder 505)
    - Fed - Few (Box 28, Folder 506)
    - Fid - Fisher, George (Box 28, Folder 507)
    - Fisher, James - Fle (Box 28, Folder 508)
    - Fli - Fon (Box 28, Folder 509)
    - For - Fos (Box 28, Folder 510)
    - Fou - Frar (Box 28, Folder 511)
    - Fras - Fri (Box 28, Folder 512)
    - Fro - Fy (Box 28, Folder 513)
    - Fagley, Richard M., 1941-1947 (Box 28, Folder 514)
    - Fahs, Charles, 1915- 1940 (Box 28, Folder 515)
    - Fahs, Charles, 1941-1944 (Box 28, Folder 516)
    - Fahs, Charles, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 517)
    - Fahs, Charles, 1946-1948, nd (Box 28, Folder 518)
    - Fairfield, Wynn C., 1940-1952 (Box 28, Folder 519)
    - Falconer, Robert and Sophie, 1941-1953 (Box 28, Folder 520)
    - Farquhar, J.N., 1907-1910 (Box 29, Folder 521)
    - Farquhar, J.N., 1911 (Box 29, Folder 522)
    - Farquhar, J.N., 1922-1923 (Box 29, Folder 523)
    - Farrand, Livingston, 1921-1933 (Box 29, Folder 524)
    - Farwell, John V., 1928-1942 (Box 29, Folder 525)
    - Faunce, W.H.P., 1900-1928 (Box 29, Folder 526)
    - Federation of South American YMCA's, 1940-1951 (Box 29, Folder 527)
    - Feng, Yu Hsiang, 1947-1948 (Box 29, Folder 528)
    - Fenn, S.P., 1915-1924 (Box 29, Folder 529)
    - Fenn, S.P., 1925-1927 (Box 29, Folder 530)
    - Fenn, S.P., 1929-1932 (Box 29, Folder 531)
    - Fermaud, Charles, 1908-1912,1932 (Box 29, Folder 532)
    - Findlay, William H., 1915, 1918 (Box 29, Folder 533)
    - Finley, John, 1924-1930 (Box 29, Folder 534)
    - First Federal Savings and Loan Association Orlando, 1942-1949 (Box 29, Folder 535)
    - Fisher, Galen M. 1908-19S5 (Box 29, Folder 536)
    - Fisher, Geoffrey F., 1945-1950 (Box 29, Folder 537)
    - Fitch, George A., 1940-1949 (Box 29, Folder 538)
    - Fleming H. Revell Co., Publishers, 1941-1944 (Box 30, Folder 539)
    - Flint, Charles A., 1930-1939 (Box 30, Folder 540)
    - Flint, Charles A., 1940-1952 (Box 30, Folder 541)
    - Floyd, ArYa C., 1943-1944 (Box 30, Folder 542)
    - Florovsky, George, 1949-1952 (Box 30, Folder 543)
    - Foch, Ferdinand, 1921 (Box 30, Folder 544)
    - Fondren, Ella, 1948-1954 (Box 30, Folder 545)
    - Ford, Edsel, 1923 (Box 30, Folder 546)
    - Ford, Mrs. Henry, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 547)
    - Foreign Missions Conference of North America, 1942,1944 (Box 30, Folder 548)
    - Forrester-Paton, John, 1934-1947 (Box 30, Folder 549)
    - Forrester-Paton, John, 1948-1954 (Box 30, Folder 550)
    - Fortune Magazine, 1940-1942 (Box 30, Folder 551)
    - Fosdick, Harry Emerson, 1906-1949 (Box 30, Folder 552)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1917-1948 (Box 30, Folder 553)
    - Foster, John W., 1907-1910, nd (Box 30, Folder 554)
    - Foster, Perley A., 1941-1949 (Box 30, Folder 555)
    - Foster, W.H.T., 1942-1948 (Box 30, Folder 556)
    - Fowler, J. Hartley, 1943-1954 (Box 30, Folder 557)
    - Francis, Alexander, 1903 (Box 30, Folder 558)
    - Fraser, Donald, 1899-1935 (Box 30, Folder 559)
    - Freeman, Fred B., 1944-1945 (Box 30, Folder 560)
    - Freeman, James E., 1932-1943 (Box 30, Folder 561)
    - French Student Christian Federation, 1915 (Box 30, Folder 562)
    - Fries, Karl, 1902-1914 (Box 31, Folder 563)
    - Fries, Karl, 1915-1921 (Box 31, Folder 564)
    - Fries, Karl, 1922 May-Jun (Box 31, Folder 565)
    - Fries, Karl, 1922 Jul-Dec (Box 31, Folder 566)
    - Fries, Karl, 1923 Jan-Mar (Box 31, Folder 567)
    - Fries, Karl, 1923 .May-Sep (Box 31, Folder 568)
    - Fries, Karl, 1923 Oct-Dec (Box 31, Folder 569)
    - Fries, Karl, 1924 Jan-Apr (Box 31, Folder 570)
    - Fries, Karl, 1924 May-Aug (Box 31, Folder 571)
    - Fries, Karl, 1924-1925 Jul (Box 31, Folder 572)
    - Fries, Karl, 1925 Sep-1926 (Box 31, Folder 573)
    - Fries, Karl, 1927-1929 (Box 31, Folder 574)
    - Fries, Karl, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 575)
    - Fries, Karl, 1933-1934 (Box 31, Folder 576)
    - Fries, Karl, 1935-1938 (Box 31, Folder 577)
    - Fries, Karl, 1939-1942 (Box 31, Folder 578)
    - Fries, Karl, 1943-1946 (Box 31, Folder 579)
    - Fries, Karl, nd (Box 31, Folder 580)
    - Frosht, John B., 1940-1953 (Box 32, Folder 581)
    - Fry, Wilfred and Anna, 1911-1937 (Box 32, Folder 582)
    - Fry, Wilfred and Anna, 1939-1941 (Box 32, Folder 583)
    - Fry, Wilfred and Anna, 1942-1948, nd. (Box 32, Folder 584)
    - Gai - Gap (Box 32, Folder 585)
    - Gar - Gay (Box 32, Folder 586)
    - Ge (Box 32, Folder 587)
    - Gi - G1 (Box 32, Folder 588)
    - God - Goo (Box 32, Folder 589)
    - Gor - Green (Box 32, Folder 590)
    - Greene - Gregg (Box 32, Folder 591)
    - Gri - Gru (Box 32, Folder 592)
    - Gu - Gw (Box 32, Folder 593)
    - Gailey, Robert R., 1935-1950 (Box 32, Folder 594)
    - Gainfort, James W., 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 595)
    - Gairdner, W.H.T., 1894-1925 (Box 32, Folder 596)
    - Gallagher, W.J., 1943-1947 (Box 32, Folder 597)
    - Galland, Emmanuel, 1915-1945 (Box 32, Folder 598)
    - Gamble, Cecil H., 1941-1943 (Box 32, Folder 599)
    - Gandhi, Mahandas Karanchand, 1934-1947 (Box 32, Folder 600)
    - Garbett, Cyril Forster, 1942-1949 (Box 32, Folder 601)
    - Gardiner, Robert H., 1905-1912 (Box 33, Folder 602)
    - Gary, E.H., 1920-1924 (Box 33, Folder 603)
    - Gascoyne-Cecil, Lord William, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 604)
    - Gennathios, Metropolitan of Thessaloniki, 1931-1938 (Box 33, Folder 605)
    - Gethman, Helen King, 1939-1952 (Box 33, Folder 606)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1926-1928 Feb (Box 33, Folder 607)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1928 May-Dec (Box 33, Folder 608)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1929 Jan-Jun (Box 33, Folder 609)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1929 Jul-Dec (Box 33, Folder 610)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1930 Jan-Mar (Box 33, Folder 611)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1930 Apr-May (Box 33, Folder 612)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1930 Jun-Dec (Box 33, Folder 613)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1931 Jan-Apr (Box 33, Folder 614)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1931 May-Jul (Box 33, Folder 615)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1931 Aug-Dec (Box 33, Folder 616)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1932 Jan-May (Box 33, Folder 617)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1932 Jun-Dec (Box 33, Folder 618)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1933-1934 Jan (Box 33, Folder 619)
    - Gethman, Walter W., 1934 Feb-1938 (Box 33, Folder 620)
    - Gibson, Betty D., 1926-1936 (Box 34, Folder 621)
    - Gibson, Betty D., 1937 (Box 34, Folder 622)
    - Gibson, Betty D., 1938 Jan-Jun (Box 34, Folder 623)
    - Gibson, Betty D., 1938 Jul-Aug (Box 34, Folder 624)
    - Gibson, Betty D., 1938 Sep-Dec (Box 34, Folder 625)
    - Gibson, Betty D., 1939-1941 (Box 34, Folder 626)
    - Gibson, Betty D., 1942-1952 (Box 34, Folder 627)
    - Gilkey, Charles W., 1903-1946 (Box 34, Folder 628)
    - Gill, C.H., 1942-1947 (Box 34, Folder 629)
    - Gleason, George, 1915-1907 (Box 34, Folder 630)
    - Glover, T.R., 1914-1940 (Box 34, Folder 631)
    - Gollock, G.A., 1923 (Box 34, Folder 632)
    - Gompers, Samuel, 1921-1923 (Box 34, Folder 633)
    - Goodall, Norman, 1944-1946 (Box 34, Folder 634)
    - Goodall, Norman, 1947-1952 (Box 34, Folder 635)
    - Goodsell, Fred Field, 1924-1941 (Box 34, Folder 636)
    - Goodsell, Fred Field, 1942-1952 (Box 34, Folder 637)
    - Gordon, M.L., 1900 (Box 35, Folder 638)
    - Goto, Shimpei, 1917-1929 (Box 35, Folder 639)
    - Goucher, John F., 1902-1911 (Box 35, Folder 640)
    - Grant, E.W., 1941-1942 (Box 35, Folder 641)
    - Gounaris, 1921 (Box 35, Folder 642)
    - Greer, David H., 1908-1917 (Box 35, Folder 643)
    - Grenfell, Wilfred T., 1918 (Box 35, Folder 644)
    - Grew, Joseph C., 1935-1949 (Box 35, Folder 645)
    - Grey of Fallodon, 1916-1920 (Box 35, Folder 646)
    - Guild, Roy B., 1941-1945 (Box 35, Folder 647)
    - Guillon, Charles, 1928-1937 (Box 35, Folder 648)
    - Guillon, Charles, 1938-1941 (Box 35, Folder 649)
    - Guillon, Charles, 1942-1951 (Box 35, Folder 650)
    - Guinness, Paul, 1946-1953 (Box 35, Folder 651)
    - Gunning, J.W., 1908-1913 (Box 35, Folder 652)
    - Guttery, Arthur M., 1933-1945 (Box 36, Folder 653)
    - Gwynne, Lewellynn, 1924-1947 (Box 36, Folder 654)
    - Haa - Hai (Box 36, Folder 655)
    - Hal - Ham (Box 36, Folder 656)
    - Han - Harl (Box 36, Folder 657)
    - Harm - Harw (Box 36, Folder 658)
    - Has - Haz (Box 36, Folder 659)
    - Hea - Hem (Box 36, Folder 660)
    - Hen - Hew (Box 36, Folder 661)
    - Hi - Hn (Box 36, Folder 662)
    - Hob - Hog (Box 36, Folder 663)
    - Hol (Box 36, Folder 664)
    - Hom - Hor (Box 36, Folder 665)
    - Hos - Hov (Box 36, Folder 666)
    - How - Hr (Box 36, Folder 667)
    - Hua - Huf (Box 36, Folder 668)
    - Hug - Hy (Box 36, Folder 669)
    - Hadley, Arthur Twining, 1908-1916, nd (Box 37, Folder 670)
    - Halifax, 1st Earl of, Edward F.L. Wood, 1936-1946 (Box 37, Folder 671)
    - Hall, Charles Cuthbert, 1900-1904 (Box 37, Folder 672)
    - Hall, Lawrence K., 1941-1947 (Box 37, Folder 673)
    - Hall, Lawrence K., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 674)
    - Hall, Lawrence K., 1949 (Box 37, Folder 675)
    - Hall, Lawrence K., 1950-1954 (Box 37, Folder 676)
    - Hall, Rosetta S., 1940-1947 (Box 37, Folder 677)
    - Hall of Fame: New York University, 1935 (Box 37, Folder 678)
    - Hallam, Wirt W., 1939-1944 (Box 37, Folder 679)
    - Halsey, Stuart and Co., 1940 (Box 37, Folder 680)
    - Halsey, Stuart and Co., 1940-1948 (Box 37, Folder 681)
    - Hamsher, M.R., 1944-1945 (Box 37, Folder 682)
    - Hanna, A.J., 1943-1955 (Box 37, Folder 683)
    - Hanson, A. Wayne, 1921-1952 (Box 37, Folder 684)
    - Harada, Tasudu, 1913-1931 (Box 37, Folder 685)
    - Harbison, Ralph W., 1941-1949 (Box 37, Folder 686)
    - Harbison, William Albert, 1941-1949 (Box 37, Folder 687)
    - Harding, Warren G., 1920-1922 (Box 38, Folder 688)
    - Harkness, Edward S., 1903-1939 (Box 38, Folder 689)
    - Harlow, Ralph, 1947-1954 (Box 38, Folder 690)
    - Harmon, Francis S., 1931-1952 (Box 38, Folder 691)
    - Harmon, Nolan B., 1945-1946 (Box 38, Folder 692)
    - Harner, Guy S., 1940-1948 (Box 38, Folder 693)
    - Harper and Brothers, 1939-1948 (Box 38, Folder 694)
    - Harper, Samuel N., 1917-1922, nd. (Box 38, Folder 695)
    - Harper, William R., 1890 (Box 38, Folder 696)
    - Harris, Frederick, 1918-1948 (Box 38, Folder 697)
    - Harris, Norman Dwight, 1944-1954 (Box 38, Folder 698)
    - Harrison, Carlton, 1928-1952 (Box 38, Folder 699)
    - Hart, Walter T., 1940-1948 (Box 38, Folder 700)
    - Harte, Archibald C., 1908-1917 (Box 38, Folder 701)
    - Harte, Archibald C., 1918-1921 (Box 38, Folder 702)
    - Harte, Archibald C., 1922-1925 (Box 38, Folder 703)
    - Harte, Archibald C., 1926-1939 (Box 38, Folder 704)
    - Harte, Archibald C., 1940-1943 (Box 38, Folder 705)
    - Harte, Archibald C., 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 706)
    - Hartenstein, Karl, 1938-1949 (Box 39, Folder 707)
    - Hartman, Lewis 0., 1940-1951 (Box 39, Folder 708)
    - Hartzell, Joseph C., 1907-1910 (Box 39, Folder 709)
    - Haskett, Walter F., 1944-1948 (Box 39, Folder 710)
    - Hathaway, Frank A., 1940-1943 (Box 39, Folder 711)
    - Hawk, Eugene B., 1940 (Box 39, Folder 712)
    - Hawkins, F.H., 1931-1933 (Box 39, Folder 713)
    - Haworth, Lester C., 1924-1950 (Box 39, Folder 714)
    - Hayes, Will H., 1922-1946 (Box 39, Folder 715)
    - Heeney, Arnold, 1941-1950 (Box 39, Folder 716)
    - Heeney, Bertal, 1940-1952 (Box 39, Folder 717)
    - Heinz, Howard J., Jr., 1941-1944 (Box 39, Folder 718)
    - Helde, George G., 1944-1946 (Box 39, Folder 719)
    - Hemingway, Charles R., 1940-1946 (Box 39, Folder 720)
    - Hennig, P.O., 1913-1916 (Box 39, Folder 721)
    - Henriod, Henry L., 1920-1923 (Box 39, Folder 722)
    - Henriod, Henry L., 1924 Feb-Jun (Box 39, Folder 723)
    - Henriod, Henry L., 1924 Jul-Dec (Box 39, Folder 7724)
    - Henriod, Henry L., 1925 (Box 39, Folder 725)
    - Henriod, Henry L., 1926 Feb-Sep (Box 39, Folder 726)
    - Henriod, Henry L., 1926 Oct-Dec (Box 39, Folder 727)
    - Henriod, Henry L., 1927 Jan-Mar (Box 39, Folder 728)
    - Henriod, Henry L., 1927 Apr-Dec (Box 39, Folder 729)
    - Henriod, Henry L., 1928-1929 (Box 39, Folder 730)
    - Henriod, Henry L., 1931-1937 (Box 40, Folder 131)
    - Henriod, Henry L., 1940-1951 (Box 40, Folder 732)
    - Hering, Hollis W., 1940-1949 (Box 40, Folder 733)
    - Herman, Harry C., 1928-1942 (Box 40, Folder 734)
    - Hermann, Harold L., 1951, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 735)
    - Herrick, Myron T., 1918 (Box 40, Folder 736)
    - Herschleb, Charles A., 1923-1952 (Box 40, Folder 737)
    - Hibbard, Carlisle V., 1915-1943 (Box 40, Folder 738)
    - Hibbard, Carlisle V., 1944-1945 (Box 40, Folder 739)
    - Hibbard, Carlisle V., 1946-1947 (Box 40, Folder 740)
    - Hibbard, Carlisle V., 1948-1954, nd. (Box 40, Folder 741)
    - Hicks, Harry Wade, 1941-1946 (Box 40, Folder 742)
    - Higdon, E.K., 1935-1949 (Box 40, Folder 743)
    - Higginbottom, Sam, 1929-1953 (Box 40, Folder 744)
    - Higginbottom, Sam, 1954-1955, nd. (Box 40, Folder 745)
    - Hobbs, Bruno, 1900-1901 (Box 41, Folder 746)
    - Hobson, Henry W., 1939-1948 (Box 41, Folder 747)
    - Hocking, William Ernest, 1928-1935, nd. (Box 41, Folder 748)
    - Hodge, George E., 1940-1948 (Box 41, Folder 749)
    - Hodge, J.Z., 1935-1947 (Box 41, Folder 750)
    - Houghton, Roy M., 1940-1947 (Box 42, Folder 778)
    - Howard, George P., 1940-1951 (Box 42, Folder 779)
    - Huber, Max, 1941-1949 (Box 42, Folder 780)
    - Huckabee, Weyman C., 1941-1945 (Box 42, Folder 781)
    - Hughes, Charles E., 1922-1931 (Box 42, Folder 782)
    - Hull, Cordell, 1939-1954 (Box 42, Folder 783)
    - Hume, Edward H., 1940-1945 (Box 42, Folder 784)
    - Hume, Wilson M., 1934-1953 (Box 42, Folder 785)
    - Hunter, D.A., 1906-1935 (Box 42, Folder 786)
    - Hunter, John L., 1940-1951 (Box 42, Folder 787)
    - Huntington, Elizabeth Dodge and George, 1930-1954 (Box 42, Folder 788)
    - Hunton, W.A., 1897-1943 (Box 42, Folder 789)
    - Hurley, Leonard F., 1944 (Box 43, Folder 790)
    - Hurrey, Charles D. 19o7-l923 (Box 43, Folder 791)
    - Hurrey, Charles D., 1924-1946 (Box 43, Folder 792)
    - Hurrey, Charles D., 1947-1952 (Box 43, Folder 793)
    - Hutchins, Francis S., 1944-1947 (Box 43, Folder 794)
    - Hutchins, William J., 1928-1945, nd. (Box 43, Folder 795)
    - Hyde, A.A., 1915-1931 (Box 43, Folder 796)
    - I (Box 43, Folder 797)
    - Ibuka, Kajinosuke, 1897-1935 (Box 43, Folder 798)
    - Iglehart, Charles W., 1940-1947 (Box 43, Folder 799)
    - Indian Association of America, Inc., 1937 (Box 43, Folder 800)
    - Ingalls, Harold B., 1942-1945 (Box 43, Folder 801)
    - Ingram, G. Ilaley, 1942-1944 (Box 43, Folder 802)
    - Ingram, George S., 1936-1951 (Box 43, Folder 803)
    - Innes, T. Christie, 1941-1947 (Box 43, Folder 804)
    - Internal Revenue Service, 1930-1954 (Box 43, Folder 805)
    - International Missionary Council, 1925-1941,1952 (Box 43, Folder 806)
    - International Review of Missions Interseminary Movement in the US(see: A. Tolbert), 1940-1947 (Box 43, Folder 807)
    - Irving, George (Box 43, Folder 808)
    - Ja (Box 44, Folder 809)
    - Jo - Ji (Box 44, Folder 810)
    - Joh (Box 44, Folder 811)
    - Jon - Ju (Box 44, Folder 812)
    - Jabavu, D.D., 1928,1934 (Box 44, Folder 813)
    - Jackson, Mary A., 1914 (Box 44, Folder 814)
    - Jacob, Ernest 0., 1911-1952 (Box 44, Folder 815)
    - James, Arthur Curtiss, 1916-1947 (Box 44, Folder 816)
    - James, D. Willis, 1907 (Box 44, Folder 817)
    - Jarvie, James N., 1915-1928 (Box 44, Folder 818)
    - Jenkins, Edward C., 1909-1953 (Box 44, Folder 819)
    - Jenny, Arnold E., 1945-1949 (Box 44, Folder 820)
    - Jerome, Percy F., 1940-1955 (Box 44, Folder 821)
    - Jessup, Walter A., 1941-1942 (Box 44, Folder 822)
    - Johannot, Henri, 1928-1935 (Box 44, Folder 823)
    - Johannot, Henri, 1936-1947 1953 (Box 44, Folder 824)
    - John, Griffith, 1898 (Box 44, Folder 825)
    - Johnson, Alba B., 1917 (Box 44, Folder 826)
    - Johnson, Edward H., 1948-1951 (Box 44, Folder 827)
    - Johnson, Edward H., 1952-1954 (Box 44, Folder 828)
    - Johnston, O.T., 1928-1940 Mar (Box 45, Folder 829)
    - Johnston, O.T., 1940-Apr-Dec (Box 45, Folder 830)
    - Johnston, O.T., 1941 (Box 45, Folder 831)
    - Johnston, O.T., 1942 (Box 45, Folder 832)
    - Johnston, O.T., 1943 (Box 45, Folder 833)
    - Johnston' O.T., 1944 (Box 45, Folder 834)
    - Johnston, O.T., 1945-1946 (Box 45, Folder 835)
    - Johnston, O.T., 1947-1951 (Box 45, Folder 836)
    - Joliot-Curie, F., 1951 (Box 45, Folder 837)
    - Jones' Arthur H., 1941-1942 (Box 45, Folder 838)
    - Jones, E. Stanley, 1935-1953 (Box 45, Folder 839)
    - Jones' Rufus W., 1920-1947 (Box 45, Folder 840)
    - Jones, Thomas Jesse, 1927-1946 (Box 45, Folder 841)
    - Jordan, Parker P., 1940-1944 (Box 45, Folder 842)
    - Jorgensen, Arthur, 1909- 1948 (Box 45, Folder 843)
    - Jowett, J.H., 1914-1916 (Box 45, Folder 844)
    - Juliana of the Netherlands, 1941-1944 (Box 45, Folder 845)
    - Ka (Box 46, Folder 846)
    - Ke (Box 46, Folder 847)
    - Ki (Box 46, Folder 848)
    - K1 - Kn (Box 46, Folder 849)
    - Ko - Kr (Box 46, Folder 850)
    - Ku - Ky (Box 46, Folder 851)
    - Kagawa, Toyohiko, 1931-1951 (Box 46, Folder 852)
    - Kaign, Raymond P., 1940-1953 (Box 46, Folder 853)
    - Kawai, Michi, 1927-1954 (Box 46, Folder 854)
    - Kawashiri, Seishu, 1926-1932 (Box 46, Folder 855)
    - Keeny, S.M., 1940-1946 (Box 46, Folder 856)
    - Keller, Adolf, 1935-1946 (Box 46, Folder 857)
    - Kelly, Herbert, 1912-1915 (Box 46, Folder 858)
    - Kennedy, Emma B., 1912-1923 (Box 46, Folder 859)
    - Kelsey, Earl H., 1940-1943 (Box 46, Folder 860)
    - Keppel, F.P., 1918-1942 (Box 46, Folder 861)
    - Kerr, Annie, 1940-1943 (Box 46, Folder 862)
    - Killam, Lloyd R., 1941-1944 (Box 46, Folder 863)
    - King, Henry H., 1940-1953 (Box 46, Folder 864)
    - King, Richard H., 1915-1941 (Box 46, Folder 865)
    - King, W.L. MacKenzie, 1915-1949 (Box 46, Folder 866)
    - Kinnaird, Emily, 1912-1947 (Box 47, Folder 867)
    - Kirby, Allan P., 1941-1943 (Box 47, Folder 868)
    - Kirby, Fred M., 1926-1936 (Box 47, Folder 869)
    - Kirman, E.C., 1944-1954 (Box 47, Folder 870)
    - Kitchen, Wilmer J., 1950-1953 (Box 47, Folder 871)
    - Kling, H.F., 1898-1912 (Box 47, Folder 872)
    - Knapp, Forrest L., 1940-1947 (Box 47, Folder 873)
    - Koechlin, Alphons, 1926- 1953 (Box 47, Folder 874)
    - Kohlstedt, Edward D., 1940 (Box 47, Folder 875)
    - Koo, T.Z., 1925-1951 (Box 47, Folder 876)